Guide to the Ira Silverberg Papers MSS.110
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Group 1, Series IX: Burroughs
  - Correspondence-Grauerholz/Silverberg email, undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence-Grauerholz/Silverberg email, undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence-Grauerholz/Silverberg email, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence-Grauerholz/Silverberg email, undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence-Grauerholz/Silverberg email, undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence-Grauerholz/Silverberg email, undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence-re: Naked Lunch Club in L.A., undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence-Silverberg re: Burroughs Projects, undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - American Academy of Arts and Letters-Burroughs Tribute 4/7/98, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Articles-Obituaries, Memorials, and Condolences, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Articles re: Burroughs, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Burroughs Bibliography, 1953-1985 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Burroughs Chat Forum, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Editorial Consultant Agreement Between Silverberg and Grove/Atlantic re: Burroughs, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Grove/Atlantic Publishing Agreement for Burroughs Projects, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Events-Invitations to Burroughs Events, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Events-Allen Ginsberg Photography Exhibit, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Miami Book Fair-Newsletter 1997 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Miami Book Fair Nov-97, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Miami Book Fair-Burroughs/Ginsberg Tribute Video 11/22/97, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - New School/St. Mark's Poetry Project-Burroughs Tribute-Corrspondence Feb-99, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - New School/St. Mark's Poetry Project-Burroughs Tribute-Flyers and Publicity Feb-99, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - New School/St. Mark's Poetry Project-Burroughs Tribute-Silverberg's Introduction and Reader Bios. Feb-99, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - New School/St. Mark's Poetry Project-Burroughs Tribute-Press Releases, Mailing Lists, and Guests Feb-99, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Photographs-Postcards/Photographs of Burroughs, Photograph of Grauerholz, Norse, Silverberg, and Photograph of Silverberg and Burroughs, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Photographs-Burroughs Reading Rigor Mortis, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Burroughs, William S.-Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Web Sites re: Burroughs, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Group 1, Series X: Ephemera
  Scope and Contents note
  One box containing Jacqueline Susann publicity from Grove Press
  - Jacqueline Susann publicity from Grove Press, undated (Box 51)
- Group 1, Series XI: J.T. Leroy
  - LeRoy - articles and fiction features, 2003-2007 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Leroy clippings, 2000-2005 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - LeRoy clippings, 2005-2007 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - LeRoy Correspondence, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - LeRoy Correspondence, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - LeRoy Correspondence, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - LeRoy Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - LeRoy Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - LeRoy - foreign publishers, 2005, undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - LeRoy - Harold's End reviews, 2004-2006 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - LeRoy - The Heart is Deceitful Above All Things reviews, 2001-2002 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - J.T. LeRoy - Hoax?, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - LeRoy - PR, book cover proofs, announcements, 2001-2003, undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - LeRoy - Sarah reviews, 2001-2001 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Morse Partners, undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Group 2, Series I: Correspondence
  - Cooper, Dennis-International Publicity, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Chua, Lawrence-Gold By the Inch-Cover Art, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Pauvert, Jean-Jacques - Contracts, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Savage, Jon-Publicity, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Cover Art, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Publicity, Reviews, Tear Sheets, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Group 2, Series II: Manuscripts
  - Cooper, Dennis-Jerk (galleys), undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Lotringer, Sylv-Consumed By Myths (galleys), undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Group 2, Series IV: Business/Administrative Files
  - Subseries A: General Business/Administration Files
    - Book Reviews, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Budget, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-High Risk Posters, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - United Nations Poster, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Group 2, Series VIII: Books/Periodicals
  - Bookforum, Winter 1998 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Express Books Literary Supplement, Jan. 1998 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Look, vol. 31, no. 18, 9/5/1967 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - The Saturday Evening Post, 1/25/1969 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - The Village Voice, vol. XLIII, no. 26, 6/30/1998 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Group 2, Series IX: Burroughs
  - Burroughs-Gladstone Media Corporation-"The Beats" 1999 Calendar (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Burroughs-Obituaries, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Group 3, Series I: Correspondence
  - Corr: Acker, Kathy, 1986-1994, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Corr: Acker, Kathy (related), 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Corr: Acker, Kathy (related), 1987, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Corr: Ackroyd, Peter, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Corr: Michael Alago, 1993-1997 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Corr: "Alex" (last name unknown), 2000 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Corr: American Booksellers Asociation, 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Corr: AmFar, May, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Corr: Apfelschmitt, Carl, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Corr: Axinn, Michael, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Corr: Keith Banner, February 10, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Corr: Barker, Clive, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Corr: Barrat, Martine, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Corr: Beam, Thom, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Corr: Beek, Mary, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Corr: Bell, Susan, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Corr: Bellamy, Dodie, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Corr: Berman, Tosh, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Corr: Birnie, Ian, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Corr: Bode, Walter and Rossett, Lisa, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Corr: Bogner, Elizabeth, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Corr: Borowski, Elizabeth, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Corr: Bornstein, Kate and Sullivan, Caitlin (related), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Corr: Bouldrey, Brian, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Corr: Gigi Bradford, June, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Corr: Brandston, Sara, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Corr: Brandt, Eric, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Corr: Cynthia A. Brehm, December 20, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Corr: Brown, Rebecca, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Corr: Brownstein, Michael, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Corr: Callahan, J., 1994 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Corr: Christy, George, 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Corr: Chua, Larry, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Corr: Colton, Jennifer, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Corr: Connor, Peter, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Corr: Cooper, Dennis, 1987-1994 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Corr: Cooper, Dennis (related), 1987-1998 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Corr: Davies, Tod, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Corr: David, Allison, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Corr: Re DeAgostini Editions, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Corr: DelSol, Michael, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Corr: Dewees, Jason, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Corr: Dowling, J., 1993 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Ebersole, Lucinda, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Einhorn, Amy, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Exact Change Correspondence, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Exact Change Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Exact Change Yearbook no. 1 Memos and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Corr: Finley, Karen, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Corr: Flanagan, Bob, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Corr: Fournier, David, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Franklin, Timothy, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Corr: Friedman, Mack, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Corr: Gerstler, Amy and Beyond Baroque, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Corr: Getty, Ann, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Corr: Ginsburg, Allen, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Corr: Ginsberg, Peter, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Corr: Goldin, Nan, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Corr: Richard Grossman, 1993-1997 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, July 1985 - October 1985 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, November, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, December, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, January, 1986 - June, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, May 1986 - June 1986 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, July, 1986 - September, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, October, 1986 - December, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, January, 1987 - June, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, July, 1987 - December, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Grove Press Correspondence re Drama News, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, January, 1988 - February, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, March, 1988 - September, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, October, 1988 - November, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, December, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, January, 1989 - February, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, March, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, April, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, May, 1989 - June, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, July, 1989 - December, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Grove Press Correspondence, 1999 - 2001 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Corr: Gutter Press, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Corr: Gutter Press, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Corr: Hake, Peter, June, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Corr: Halpern, Daniel (re Dennis Cooper), June 7, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Corr: Hannah, Duncan, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Corr: Hell, Richard, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Corr. re High Risk, 1988-2001 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Corr. re High Risk 2, 1991-1994 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Corr: Hollander, Kurt, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Corr: Huston, Bo, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Corr: Indiana, Gary (related), 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Ira Silverberg Communications Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Corr: Jane (last name unknown), undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Corr: Justin, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Corr: Kane, Bill, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Corr: Alexander Karinsky, June 7, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Corr: Pamala Karol (aka La Loca), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Corr: Katzenberger, Elaine, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Corr: Killian, Kevin, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Corr: Killian, Patrick, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Corr: Robert Klanten, February 6, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Corr: Klayman, Rachel (re High Risk), 1990-1992 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Corr: Kolovakos, Gregory, 1988-1992 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Corr: Gregory Kolovakos and Gary Indiana, November 2, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Corr: Kriv, Arlene, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Corr: Lassell, Michael, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Corr: Latino Writers Roundtable, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Leary, Timothy, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Corr: Lee, Linda, May 24, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Corr: Levine, Jane, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Corr: Lewis, Stacey, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Corr: Linden, Millicent, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Armando Manalo, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Manrique, Jaime, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Corr: Mark, P.J., 1993 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Corr: Martinelli, Gabriella, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Corr: Matthews, William, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Corr: McManus, Jim, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Corr: McNeace, Richard, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Corr: Miller, Arthur (and related), 1987 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Corr: Miller, Nancy, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Corr: Morris, Bob, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Corr: Mueller, Cookie, 1984-1993 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Corr: Naher, Gaby, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Corr: Norwich, Billy, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Corr: Nosowsky, Ethan, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Corr: Doug Nufer, June, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Corr: Owens, Kurt, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Corr: Paper Magazine, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Corr: Patty, March 11, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Corr: Paul, Don, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Corr: Peters, Nancy, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Corr: Poole, Jeff, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Corr: Preston, John, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Corr: Pullinger, Kate, 1987-1994 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Corr: Pulsifer, Gary, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Corr: Purdy, James, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Corr: Rachlin, Nahid, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Corr: Raikow, Ian, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Corr: John Rechy, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Corr: Rist, Darrell Yates, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Corr: Milton J. Rosenberg, undated (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Corr: Rower, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Corr: D. Ruben, 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Corr: Samansohn, Karen, undated (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Corr: Ruff, Shawn Stewart, July, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Corr: Scholder, Amy, 1987-1994 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Larry Schubert, 1997, undated (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence: Sedaris, David and Publishment Contracts, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Corr: Sellers, Terrence, 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Corr: Serio, Jocelyn, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Corr: Serpent's Tail, 1990-1997 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Corr: Simon, Kate, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Corr: Skinner, Deborah, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Corr: Slovak, Paul, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Corr: Smith, Liz, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Corr: Sokolowski, Thomas, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Corr: F. Robert Stein, August, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Corr: Stewart, Tabori and Cheng, 1988-1996 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Corr: Stockly, Charles, 1990-1992 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Corr: Sussler, Betsy, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Corr: Swados, Robin, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Corr: Tabori, Lena, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Corr: Tim Teeman, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Corr: Morton Teicher, December 2, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Corr: Tenner, Suzanne, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Corr: Thom, Janice and Berkley; Marc Scott, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Corr: Tillman, Lynne, undated (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Corr: Tobias, 1989-1993 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Corr: Trinidad, David, 1989-1997 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Corr: Ulin, David, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Corr: Unknown/ Unspecified, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence: authors unknown, 1990-1994 (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Corr: Water, John, 1989-1997 (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Corr: West, Donna, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Corr: Wetherbee, Janet, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Corr: Wheeler, Susan, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Corr: Whitman, Phyllis, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Corr: Wojnarowicz, David, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Corr: Yablonsky, Linda, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Corr: Young, Elizabeth, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Corr: Zedd, Nick, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Corr: Zeppetelli, John, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Corr: Unknown/ Unspecified, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 107)
- Group 3, Series II: Manuscripts
  - Correspondence re Acker, Kathy; and Dead Doll Humility Manuscript, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Acker, Kathy - Dead Doll Humility, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - The End of the White Male World - Acker, Kathy, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Acker, Kathy - Fucking Up Japanese (excerpt), undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - William Burroughs - Kathy Acker, August 4, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Edwards in the Wilderness - Anastas, Benjamin, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript - Ausen, Alam, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Where is Love; and That's What Friends are For - Bartlett, Neil, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Distortion - Stephen Beachy (notes), undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Hunters/Gatherers - Beachy, Stephen, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lord of Dark Places - Bennett, Hal (chapters 1 and 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lord of Dark Places - Bennett, Hal (chapters 3 and 4), undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - A History of Hours - Maurice Berger (notes and research), undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Untitled Story Collection - David Bezmozgis, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Manhattan is My Beat - Bishop/ Deaver Manuscript, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Manhattan is My Beat Screenplay - Bishop/ Deaver, October, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Grief - Rebecca Brown, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Bestseller - Bumlein, Michael, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Collateral Damage - Carey, Tom, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Poems - Carey, Tom, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Islands in the Sky - Michael Carroll, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Coq au Vin - Carter, Charlotte, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Bitch Dub - Chua, Lawrence, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Encountering the American Holocaust - Churchill, Ward, undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - City Lights Catalog, Fall/Winter 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - The House of Sleep - Coe, Jonathan Part 1, undated, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - The House of Sleep - Coe, Jonathan Part 2, undated, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - The House of Sleep - Coe, Jonathan Part 3, undated, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - The Rotter's Club (extract) - Jonathan Coe, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Poems - Conway, Jeffrey, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Phoebe 2002: An Essay - Conway, Crosbie, Trinidad - Manuscripts, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Them: Selected Poems - Cooper, Dennis (copy edited), undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Try - Cooper, Dennis Part I (copy edited), undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Try - Cooper, Dennis Part 2 (copy edited), undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Try - Cooper, Dennis Part 3 (copy edited), undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Try - Cooper, Dennis Part I (copy edited), undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Try - Cooper, Dennis Part 2 (copy edited), undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Try - Cooper, Dennis Part 3 (copy edited), undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Try manuscript - 2nd half - Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The Sluts - Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Wrong - Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Counterculture - 60's material, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Counterculture - book proposal, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Courier - zine, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Poems - Caudros, Gil, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Go With the Flow - Erik Davis, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - High Risk submission: DeFazio, Michelangelo, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - By His Wild Lone (fragment) - De Gramont, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Death by Drowning - Dick, Leslie, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Powerlessness - Dlugos, Tim ch. 1, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Powerlessness - Dlugos, Tim ch. 2, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mr. Happy - Lawrence Douglas, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Saida - Ducornet, Rikki, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Things He Did - Elovitz, Marc E., 1991 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Jump Cut - Zach Emery, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Rockabilly - Field, Edward, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Filmmaker on Filmmakers - proposal, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - We Are pt. 1 - B.G. Firmani, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - We Are pt. 2 - B.G. Firmani, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - The Book of Medicine (sections) - Flanagan, Bob, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - The Plain Journal - Bob Flanagan, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - You Can Do Anything - Flander, Laura, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Red Night Miniseries - Tim Franklin, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - The Factsheet Five Zine Reader - Friedman, R. Seth - Proof Copy, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - The Wild Shot - Garciarobles and Grauerholz, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Galas, Philip Dimitri - Articles and untitled manuscript, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Untitled manuscript - Gaitskill, Mary, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - To Jacob Rabinowitz - Ginsberg, Alan - with correspondence, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Nothing is True - John Grogsby Geiger, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Bankrupting Yourself with Generosity - Giorno, John, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Great Demon Kings; and Jane Bowles' Pussy manuscripts - Giorno, John, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Great Demon Kings - John Giorno, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Giorno, John - Submissions for High Risk 2, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - I've Known the Best Minds of My Generation... - John Giorno, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - You Got to Burn to Shine - John Giorno, 1979-1985, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Dream Love - Allen Ginsburg, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - What You Were Dying to Tell Me - James Grauerholz, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - High Risk Submission - Tony Green, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard - Manuscript (photocopy) pt 1 of 3, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard - Manuscript (photocopy) pt 2 of 3, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard - Manuscript (photocopy) pt 3 of 3, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard - Bound Manuscript, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Book of Lazarus - Grossman, Richard - Bound Manuscript, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Paper Doll screenpaly - Hampton/Zitwer, June, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - The Subversive Power of Sexual Difference, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - I'm Going to Go Out Like a Fucking Meteor! - Harris, Craig G., 1992 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - The Heart Too Long Supressed - Hebard, Carol, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - High Risk manuscript (copy edited) folder 1, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - High Risk manuscript (copy edited) folder 2, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - High Risk manuscript (copy edited) folder 3, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - The Big Heat: Making and Unmaking Flaming Creatures, July 25, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Cult of the Cobra - Hoctel, Patrick, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Frenzy of the Flesh - Home, Stewart, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Uninvited - Richard House, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Dear Mr. President manuscript - Hudson, Gabe, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Dreams Involving Water - Indiana, Gary, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Rent Boy - Indiana, Gary, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - It's All True: Personal Writing from Zines - submissions and table of contents, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Half Life pt. 1 - Shelly Jackson, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Half Life pt. 2 - Shelly Jackson, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Mo' Better Malcolm - James, Darius, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Untitled Manuscript - Kabat, Jennifer, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - 1260 Heartbeats per Minute - Kertess, Klaus part 2, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - 1260 Heartbeats per Minute - Kertess, Klaus part 1, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - 1260 Heartbeats per Minute - Kertess, Klaus part 1, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Kertess, Klaus - American Standard, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Crash Course (excerpt) - Kolovakos, Gregory, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Vexations - Damon Krukowski, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Indecision pt. 1 - Benjamin Kunkel, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Indecision pt. 2 - Benjamin Kunkel, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Poems - Lassell, Michael, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Poems - Lassell, Michael, undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Poems - Lassell, Michael, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Untitled, Oil on Canvas - Latzky, Eric, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)